let questions;

var questions = [
  {
    // Question 1
    question: "1. Monica briefly dates billionaire Pete Becker. Which country does he take her for their first date?",
    answers: {
      a: "Italy",
      b: "France",
      c: "Greece",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    // Question 2
    question: "2. Rachel was popular in high school. Her prom date Chip ditched her for which girl at school?",
    answers: {
      a: "Sally Roberts",
      b: "Amy Welsh",
      c: "Valerie Thompson",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    // Question 3
    question: "3. Chandler is a unique first name, but Bing is something different! Chandler says that his last name is Gaelic for what?",
    answers: {
      a: "Huzzah! The team has scored!",
      b: "The turkey's done.",
      c: "Thou hast received a telegram.",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    // Question 4
    question: "4. How much of Joey’s heritage is Portuguese?",
    answers: {
      a: "1/4",
      b: "1/8",
      c: "1/16",
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
  {
    // Question 5
    question: "5. What fake name does Phoebe use when she wants to remain anonymous?",
    answers: {
      a: "Regina Phalange",
      b: "Bonnie Riddle",
      c: "Anastasia Beaverhausen",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    // Question 6
    question: "6. Monica and Chandler met on Thanksgiving in 1987. She pursued her career as a chef because Chandler complimented her on which dish?",
    answers: {
      a: "Mac & Cheese",
      b: "Stuffing",
      c: "Green Bean Casserole",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    // Question 7
    question: "7. When Ross and Rachel were 'on a break,' Ross slept with Chloe. Where does she work?",
    answers: {
      a: "Domino's",
      b: "Xerox",
      c: "Microsoft",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    // Question 8
    question: "8. What’s Joey’s penguin’s name?",
    answers: {
      a: "Huggsy",
      b: "Waddle",
      c: "Snowflake",
    },
    correctAnswer: "a"
  },
  {
    // Question 9
    question: "9. Janice gets married twice. What’s was her first husband’s name?",
    answers: {
      a: "Chandler Bing",
      b: "Gary Litman",
      c: "Rob Baileystock",
    },
    correctAnswer: "b"
  },
  {
    // Question 10
    question: "10. What’s the name of the 1950s-themed diner where Monica worked as a waitress?",
    answers: {
      a: "Marilyn & Audrey",
      b: "Central Perk",
      c: "Moondance Diner",
    },
    correctAnswer: "c"
  },
]